webpt.com 2015-09-05

# Privacy Policy | WebPT

Effective December 23, 2014

#### Our Commitment to Privacy

This privacy policy applies to [www.webpt.com](http://www.webpt.com/) owned and operated by WebPT. Your privacy and the privacy of your clients are very important to us. To better protect your privacy WebPT provides this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. It also describes how you can access and update this information. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

WebPT has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements ](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/)including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personally identifiable information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at:

**WebPT**  
ATTN: Website Security  
625 S. 5th St. Building A  
Phoenix, AZ 85004

If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint). The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site (www.webpt.com), and does not cover information that may be collected through our applications and behind the log in on our website.

#### The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the WebPT.com website. On some pages, you can make requests to schedule a demo. The types of personally identifiable information collected at these pages are: Name, Address, Email Address, and Phone Number.

#### The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself only to learn about your needs for EMR solutions. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the setup of your account.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive and communicate with you about WebPT’s products and services. Such addresses are not shared with outside parties.

Finally, we never use, share, sell or rent the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described in this privacy policy without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

#### Cookies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by WebPT and our marketing partners, affiliates, and analytics providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the website, tracking users’ movements around the website and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for setting user preferences and storing user activity. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as contests or surveys, will be limited.

The use of cookies by our tracking utility company is covered by our privacy policy. We do have access or control over these cookies. Our partners use session ID cookies to make it easier to navigate to our site.

#### Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we and the third party tracking services we use gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We do link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

#### Local Storage Objects

We use Local Storage Objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 [content information and preferences.] Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity also use LSOs such as HTML 5 and Flash to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

#### Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [Here](http://preferences.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

#### Frames

Some of our pages utilize framing techniques to serve content to from our partners while preserving the look and feel of our Web site. Please be aware that you are providing your personally identifiable information to these third parties and not to www.webpt.com.  

#### Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. If you wish to Opt-out of receiving these newsletters you may do so at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions within the emails you receive.

#### Service Related Announcements

We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.

#### Referrals

When you register for a demo you have the opportunity to let us know if you heard about us from somebody you know. If you do, we will give you the opportunity to provide us with your friend’s name and email address so we can credit them with a referral bonus. WebPT stores this information for the sole purpose of providing the referral bonus and tracking the success of our referral program.

If your name has been provided as a referral you may contact us at [privacy@webpt.com](mailto:info@webpt.com) to request we no longer store your name.

#### Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by WebPT. Please be aware that we, WebPT, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

#### Public Forums

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. Our blog is managed by a third party application that may require you to register to post a comment. We do not have access or control of the information posted to the blog. You will need to contact or login into the third party application if you want the personally identifiable information that was posted to the comments section removed. To learn how the third party application uses your information, please review their privacy policy.

#### Testimonials

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to request that your testimonial be removed you may do so by contacting us at [privacy@webpt.com](mailto:privacy@webpt.com).

#### Service Providers

We use other third parties such as an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf. When you sign up for our services, we will share your personally identifiable information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

#### Social Media Feature and Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook and Twitter buttons. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

#### Legal Disclosure

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law such as company subpoena, or similar legal process and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

##### Business Transitions

In the event WebPT goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information.

#### Our Commitment to Data Security

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13 for sales purposes, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. However, some of our clients may have patients who are under 13 and their information would be safely secured in our encrypted database.

#### Changes to This Policy

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

#### How You Can Access, Correct, Delete and Deactivate Your Information

You can access, delete and correct all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us at [privacy@webpt.com](mailto:privacy@webpt.com) or by submitting a written request to:

**WebPT**  
ATTN: Website Security  
625 S. 5th St. Building A  
Phoenix, AZ 85004

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [privacy@webpt.com](mailto:privacy@webpt.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows errors. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

#### How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [privacy@webpt.com](mailto:privacy@webpt.com) or write to us through the mailing address listed above.

#### **Get exclusive content** delivered right to your inbox.
